好咧  咱俩哥们
Here we are... a couple of dudes
要来点烧烤乐子了
getting ready to do some chillin' and grillin'.
我刚刚叫你哥们没问题吧
Are you okay that I just called you a dude?
放松放松哥们  我们是在烧烤
Relax, we're barbecuing.
烧烤的时候  大家都是哥们
Everybody's a dude.
太好了  正式行动啦
Okay. Let's do this.
当然咯
Absolutely.
不过  首先  我要你办点事儿
First, I need you to do a few things.
悉听尊便
Hit me. Whatever you want.
剥玉米  给肉入味
Shuck the corn? Season the meat?
修草坪
Mow the lawn.
呃  啥
Um, what?
清水管  换轮胎
And clean the gutters, rotate my tires,
补浴盆  还有洗碗
grout the tub, and empty the dishwasher.
哥们
Dude.
这些都跟烧烤八竿子打不到一块儿啊
What does that have to do with barbecuing?
我怎么就真以为你来我这儿是学东西的呢
I thought you came here to learn.
我先去修草坪
Let me go get the lawn mower.
我知道迪吉的伎俩
I knew exactly what Diggie was doing.
借烧烤之名来拉拢我这个老爸
Using barbecue to soften up the old man?
他要是想博得我的好感
If he wanted to get on my good side,
还是得先
he was going to have to get on the good side
过了日常家务这一关再说
of my to-do list.
终于  有甜头了
Finally, a little thrilla on the grilla!
家务活儿饿死人
All those chores made me hungry.
这是我的
That's mine.
怎么  你竟然忘记带你自己的牛排来了
What... did you forget to bring your own steak?
下次咯
Maybe next time.
下次
Next time?
我成功啦
I'm in! ( Laughs )
噢
Aah!
带你自己的牛排来  太经典了
"Bring your own steak." Classic!
你为什么要折磨那个可怜的孩子
Why are you messing with that poor boy?
只是确认一下他配不配得上咱们女儿
I'm just making sure he's good enough for my daughter.
真是辛苦的一天啊
And I'm done for the day.
别告诉玛蒂
Don't tell Maddie,
不过话说回来  除了他那搞笑的名字
but except for that stupid name,
迪吉那男孩其实不错
Diggie's all right.